Guide to the Sheila Wellington, Secretary of Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Sheila Wellington, secretary of Yale University, records
1984-1992
RU 350
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
5
The records consist of notebooks, appointment books and calendars, and general administrative files documenting Sheila Wellington's tenure as secretary of Yale University.
Yale University. Office of the Secretary
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 4-A (YRG 4-A), Records of the Yale secretary's office.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of notebooks, appointment books and calendars, and general administrative files documenting Sheila Wellington's tenure as secretary of Yale University.
Universities and colleges -- Administration; Wellington, Sheila W.; Yale University -- Administration; Yale Corporation; Yale University. Office of the Secretary
- Administrative records of Sheila Wellington, circa 1984-1992; Accession 1994-A-077
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2029
  - American Theatre Museum (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Animals (Correspondence 1) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Animals (Correspondence 2) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - B Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bicentennial - US Constitution, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bush Center (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Bills (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - C Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Chamber of Commerce - Women's Steering (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Corn. Services Fellow, Pat Simmonds, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Community Services, Sandy Kandel, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - CT Educ. Policy Seminar, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - CT Dept. of Higher Educ., 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - CT Legislature and Meetings, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - CT Popular Bank, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - DisabiIities, 1984-1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Dixwell Q House, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Environmental Policy Commission (Sabin), 1989 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Fair Haven (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Foreign Students and Scholars, 1987-1991 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - French Department, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Green Party, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - I Have a Dream, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Center for International and Area Studies, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - International Center, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Dr. Koh, US-Korea Conference, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Connecticut Seed Venture, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - NRHEDAC Minutes, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Cultural Affairs NH (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - New Haven: An Emerging City for Biotechnology - Videotape (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Phase II (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - New Haven Annual Report (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - The New Journal, 1987 September 4 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Weekly Bulletin and Calendar, 1992 June 1-8 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - CCIC Applicants and Job Description, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Anne Frank, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Gene Mapping, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - NWDCNale, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Int. Science and Engin. Fair, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Yale College Executive Committee, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Center of Technological Excellence (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - More anduse, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Nat'l Anthem, G. Pierson, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Nat'l Assoc. of Black Students for Educational Advancement, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - New Haven and Leon Sister Cities, 1986- 1989 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Occupational Medicine, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Police - Patch- Uniform (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Cole Porter, 1987-1991 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Quinnipiac College, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Recycling/Trash/Waste Disposal (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Regional Councii on Education for Employment, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Reporters, 1987-1990 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Requests for Funding: Internal (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Requests for Funding: External (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Science Park (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Sigma Xi, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - St. Petersburg TirnedPoynter, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Tampon Machines, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - TV3-WFSB, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Theroux, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - This Week at Yale, 1988-1991 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - United Church on the Green, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - United Community Nursery School, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - World Peace Messengers, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - York Square, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Accreditation, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Alum Fellow, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Berkeley (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Campus Contact (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Centro San Jose (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Chaplain Misc, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - City Approvals, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Facilities/Space, 1987-1990 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Security Agenda and Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Science Museum of CT (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - So. Africa, 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Reverse Chronological Correspondence Files
    - 1991 December (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - 1991 November (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - 1991 October (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - 1991 September (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - 1991 August (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - 1991 July (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - 1991 June (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - 1991 May (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - 1991 April (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - 1991 March (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - 1991 February (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - 1991 January (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - 1990 December (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - 1990 November (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - 1990 October (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - 1990 September (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - 1990 August (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - 1990 July (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - 1990 June (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - 1990 May (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - 1990 April (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - 1990 March (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - 1990 February (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - 1990 January (Box 4, Folder 106)
    - 1989 December (Box 4, Folder 107)
    - 1989 November (Box 4, Folder 108)
    - 1989 October (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - 1989 September (Box 4, Folder 110)
    - 1989 August (Box 4, Folder 111)
- Notebooks, appointment books, calendars, and computer files of Sheila Wellington, circa 1986-1992; Accession 1994-A-092
  - Notebooks, appointment books, and calendars of Sheila Wellington, circa 1986-1992 (Box 1–2)